Ford, Alvin; Collection apap159
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Alvin Ford Biographical, 1965-1993; 4; 0.17 cubic ft.
  This series contains newspaper and magazine articles, most of which are photocopied, about the Ford case. This series also contains a folder related to Ford's death and funeral. Also represented are a small collection of photographs of Ford at various ages and photographs of his attorneys. There is a short note from Connie Ford, Alvin's mother, to Attorney Wollan concerning a video of the Ford funeral, which is also contained in this collection. The most important resource in this series is the news clippings, which are very helpful in following the progression of the Ford case. The news clippings cover most major events in the Ford case. In addition to collecting news clippings, Laurin Wollan had an assistant visit Gainesville, Florida, where Ford was apprehended, and the assistant photocopied all articles from area papers that reported on the Ford story from 1974 to 1975.
  - Ford, Character References, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Alvin Ford Biographical), Folder 1)
  - Death of Alvin Ford, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Alvin Ford Biographical), Folder 2)
  - Ford, Connie, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Alvin Ford Biographical), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1974-1981 (Box 1 (4-Alvin Ford Biographical), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1982-1992 (Box 1 (4-Alvin Ford Biographical), Folder 5)
  - Photographs, 1965-1993 (Box 1 (4-Alvin Ford Biographical), Folder 6)
  - Ford Funeral VHS Video, 1991 (Vhs 1)